<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-31T06:11:45-06:00</updated><id>https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Jishnu Singiresu</title><subtitle>APCSP:Tri 1</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Unit 3 Sections 17-18</title><link href="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/lesson" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unit 3 Sections 17-18" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/dd-lesson</id><author><name></name></author><category term="lessons" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithmic Efficiency and Undecidable Problems]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">College Mc</title><link href="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/2023/01/29/College-MC.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="College Mc" /><published>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/2023/01/29/College-MC</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collegeboard MC 2 Corrections and Reflections Final Score Question 11 For this question, I forgot that the and function as long as one of the conditions if true, the output will always be true and so the correct answer for this question would be “A” Question 17 For this question, the mistake that I made while doing this was that I ignored the AND, what this means is that both of the conditions have to be met for the code to return true but I failed to recognize this. The correct answer thus would be D instead of B. Question 30 For this question what I did wrong was that I rushed the question since I didn’t want to read the whole question and try each and every answer out so I just selected the option that closely resembled the 1st one and so I went with D instead of C. In the future, I should take my time. Question 38 This question I got wrong because I didn’t pay attention to the wording on the answer choices, because when I was testing the answers out, I went with an even number so I ended up generalizing all the outcomes to the same thing and so the right answer wold be C. In the future, take my time. Question 41 For this question, yet again, i rushed the question, I just chose the two options that closely resembled each other. C would restrict the voters to 1 so the right answer i D which would allow 20%. Question 43 Here, the mistake that I made was that I was looking at it from the perspective that it had to be completed thing but I failed to recognize that simulations can be used to model projects before they are even completed. Thus, the right answer is C. Question 50 This question I got wrong because I didn’t know how to convert the hexadecimal number into decimal but now after looking at the internet, I realized that its pretty easy to do, just take the first number for ex. 5, add 1 then multiply it by 5 and then add that number to the original number and you get the decimal value]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lecture Notes</title><link href="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/2023/01/24/Lecture-Notes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lecture Notes" /><published>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/2023/01/24/Lecture-Notes</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[5.1 Notes A Disrupter is something that changes the way No critical thinking exists when using ChatCPT Bias exists, causing limited perspective -&gt; lack of creativity, perspective, and maybe technology in some cases 5.1 Reflection The Beneficial Effects that My Project Provides Includes: A create interactive experience A good pass of free time when bored and just want something quick and fun to do Has a fun little competitive side to it The Potential Harmful Effects My Project has Includes: Addiction, games can lead to addiction and thus lead to harmful unhealthy habits to develop Cyberbullying is a possible threat if a player’s scores weren’t high, making them prone to being bullied online for their poor performance in games May not be completely working thus leading to a dissatisfying experience for the user of the program Dopamine Dopamine plays a crucial role in how we feel pleasure and motivation. It’s what drives us to pursue things that make us happy, whether it’s food, chatting with friends, or being rewarded. But with social media and stuff, people are becoming detoxed to this sensation. This results in the attention span of people being greatly reduced and them being more likely to be distracted since they want to feel the dopamine rush. This is a huge problem since it leads to stuff like procrastinating and this leads to and unhealthy and harmful lifestyle. And so, people shouldn’t just treat it like it’s a hoax but actually think of it as a greater problem. Internet Blockers / Admin Passwords Internet blocker can be a good thing, they often protect students and others from accessing dangerous sites, however, they also might restrict a large amount of great resources such as AWS. Admin passwords enable users and admins to ensure the safety of their experience and there aren’t any cons to having it except for it would result in large damage if the password were to be leaked or found out 5.2 Notes Not everyone has access to technology like phones and laptops like we do Some people are unable to afford or unable to access due to state of life Country regulations, Religious reasons, refuses to use technology 5.2 Reflection In a largely digital world like ours, a digital divide would mean that and unequal access to technology and knowledge would be present. This would affect things like jobs oppurtunities and education, causing a higher level of disparity between people with access and those without. Also with a large majority of mass communication and just normal day to day communication being done digitally, people would be unable to particpate in society equally, leading to some opinions not being heard and would result in a large bias.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Model and Object-Oriented Programming</title><link href="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/2023/01/10/PBL-model.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Model and Object-Oriented Programming" /><published>2023-01-10T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-10T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/2023/01/10/PBL-model</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented Programming is a part of learning Python. The objective of this blog is to introduce OOP with the intention of PBL task to create a database. The foundations for a database is defining a Class and understanding instance data and methods. A database is often a focus of backend coding as it will store persistent data, that can be recalled after the immediate session is closed.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/images/python.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/images/python.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">CPT Scoring - Week 1</title><link href="https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/ScoringCPT1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CPT Scoring - Week 1" /><published>2023-01-08T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-08T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jishnus420.github.io/CSP-tri1/CPT-Week1Scoring</id><author><name></name></author><category term="markdown" /><category term="Week 17" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week 1, CPT student score grading and reflection]]></summary></entry></feed>